Vincent Price Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Stage, Screen, and Studio Files, 1935-1992 (Box 127-200)
  - Commercials and promotions (Box 127)
    - Wesson Light Touch Shortening, 1970-1971
    - Wishbone Salad Dressing, 1971
    - Worlds of Fun, 1985
    - Zero Weed Killer, 1984
  - Films
    - The Abominable Dr. Phibes, 1970-1971, (4 folders)
    - Annabelle Lee, 1972-1973
    - Backtrack, 1988 (Box 130)
    - The Baron of Arizona, 1950
    - The Bat, 1959, undated, (2 folders)
    - Beach Party, circa 1963
    - The Big Circus, 1959, (2 folders)
    - Bloodbath at the House of Death, 1982-1983
    - Brigham Young, 1940
    - Chagall, 1963-1964, undated
    - Champagne for Caesar, 1949-1950 (Box 131)
    - The Chautauqua (released as The Trouble with Girls), 1968
    - City in the Sea, 1964, undated
    - Comedy of Terrors, 1963, (3 folders)
    - Confessions of an Opium Eater, 1961
    - Conqueror Worm (alternate title Witchfinder General), 1967-1968, (2 folders) (Box 132)
    - Cry of the Banshee, 1969-1970, undated
    - Days of Fury, 1979, undated
    - Dead Heat, 1987-1988
    - Devil's Triangle, 1970-1975
    - Diary of a Madman See Container 135, The Horla
    - Don't Scream...It's Only a Movie, 1985
    - Dr. Goldfoot and the Bikini Machine, 1965, (2 folders) (Box 133)
    - Dr. Goldfoot and the Girl Bombs, (alternate title Dr. Goldfoot and the Love Bombs), 1965-1966, (2 folders)
    - Dr. Phibes Rises Again, 1971-1972, (2 folders)
    - Dragonwyck, 1945-1946, (2 folders)
    - Edward Scissorhands, 1990 (Box 134)
    - Eve of St. Mark, 1944
    - A Few Lessons to Remember, 1988
    - The Fly, 1958, 1972
    - From a Whisper to a Scream (released as The Offspring), 1985-1988
    - The Great Mouse Detective, 1983-1992, (2 folders)
    - Green Hell, 1939-1940
    - The Haunted Palace, 1963, (2 folders)
    - His Kind of Woman, 1950 (Box 135)
    - The Horla (released as Diary of a Madman), 1962, (2 folders)
    - House of Long Shadows, 1982-1983
    - House of One Thousand Dolls, 1966-1967, (2 folders)
    - House of Seven Gables, 1940
    - House of Usher (alternate title The Fall of the House of Usher), 1959-1960, undated, (3 folders) (Box 136)
    - The House of Wax, 1953
    - House on Haunted Hill, 1958-1959, undated
    - Hudson's Bay, 1940-1941
    - The Invisible Man Returns, 1939-1940
    - Jeopardy (released as The Web), 1947
    - Journey into Fear, 1974-1976 (Box 137)
    - The Last Man on Earth, 1963, (2 folders)
    - Mad Magician, 1953-1954, undated
    - Madhouse (alternate title Revenge of Dr. Death), 1973-1974
    - Masque of the Red Death, 1963-1964, (2 folders)
    - Master of the World, 1960, (2 folders) (Box 138)
    - Miscellaneous productions, 1950, 1975-1991, undated
    - The Monster Club, 1980-1981
    - More Dead than Alive, 1968
    - Nefertite, Virgin of the Nile (released as Nefertite, Queen of the Nile, [1961], (2 folders)
    - The Oblong Box, 1968-1969, undated, (3 folders) (Box 139)
    - The Offspring See Container 134, From a Whisper to a Scream
    - Percy's Progress, 1973, (2 folders)
    - The Pit and the Pendulum, 1960-1961
    - The Private Lives of Elizabeth and Essex, 1939
    - The Raven, 1962-1963, undated
    - Reprieve (released as Convicts 4), 1961
    - Return of the Fly, 1959 (Box 140)
    - Scream and Scream Again, 1969-1970, (2 folders)
    - Serenade, 1955-1956
    - Service De Luxe, 1938-1939, (3 folders)
    - Son of Sinbad, 1953-1955 (Box 141)
    - The Song of Bernadette, 1942, (3 folders)
    - The Story of Mankind, 1956-1957, (2 folders)
    - Taboos of the World, (alternate title Taboo), 1964-1965
    - Tales of Terror, 1961-1962, (4 folders) (Box 142)
    - The Ten Commandments, 1954-1955, (3 folders)
    - Theatre of Blood, 1972-1973, (5 folders) See also Oversize
    - The Tingler, 1959 (Box 143)
    - Tomb of Ligeia, 1964-1965
    - Tower of London, 1939, 1962, (2 folders)
    - Twice Told Tales, 1962, (3 folders)
    - Vincent, 1981-1983
    - The Web See Container 136, Jeopardy
    - The Whales of August, 1986-1988, undated, (3 folders) (Box 144)
    - While the City Sleeps, 1955
    - Yellow Sky (released as The Jackals), 1966-1967, undated
  - Lectures See also Container 150, Royce Carlton, Inc.
    - 1937, 1947-1956
    - 1957-1958, (2 folders)
    - 1959-1963, (11 folders) (Box 145)
    - 1964-1968, (8 folders) (Box 146)
    - 1969-1971, (9 folders) See also Oversize (Box 147)
    - 1972-1983, (9 folders) (Box 148)
    - 1984-1987, undated, (5 folders) (Box 149)
  - Miscellaneous files
    - Business materials
      - Arthur Kennard Associates, 1965-1972, undated
      - Bill Doll and Company, 1963-1971, undated
      - Famous Artists Limited, 1980, 1987
      - International Creative Management, 1975-1988
      - International Famous Agency, 1971-1974
      - Kolmar-Luth Entertainment, 1980-1986 See also Container 150, Schedules and itineraries, and Containers 175-177, "Diversions and Delights"
      - Marmor, Arthur, 1968-1971
      - Miscellany, 1963-1992, undated (Box 150)
      - Paul Kohner, Inc., 1982-1991
      - Salkow, Lester, 1961-1973, undated
      - Schedules and itineraries, 1952, 1963-1985, undated, (3 folders) See also Containers 144-149, Lectures
      - Royce Carlton, Inc., 1980-1991 See also Container 150, Schedules and itineraries, and Containers 144-149, Lectures
      - W. Colston Leigh, Inc., 1958-1980 See also Containers 144-149, Lectures
    - Public appearances (Box 151)
      - Art shows
        - 1953-1968
        - 1969-1976, 1984
      - Canteen Corp. dinners, 1979-1980
      - Cruises
        - Bahama Cruise Line, 1985
        - Cunard, 1971, 1985-1988
        - Princess Cruises, 1970-1972, 1986-1988
        - Royal Cruise Line, 1980-1989
        - Royal Viking Line, 1980-1989, undated
        - Various engagements, 1976-1988
      - Fashion shows, 1950, 1956, 1979-1980, undated
      - Film festivals
        - 1971
        - 1980-1982
        - 1983-1986, (3 folders) (Box 152)
      - March of Dimes activities, 1984-1988, undated
      - Variety Clubs International activities, 1968-1974, 1984
      - Various events
        - 1938-1939, 1947-1959 See also Oversize
        - 1960-1979, (5 folders) (Box 153)
        - 1980-1991, undated, (5 folders) (Box 154)
    - Publicity
      - 1935-1957, (3 folders)
      - 1958-1969, (10 folders) (Box 155)
      - 1970-1992, undated, (9 folders) (Box 156)
    - Script fragments, 1956, 1966, 1983, undated (Box 157)
    - Scripts submitted
      - 1948-1954, (6 folders)
      - 1955-1957, (6 folders) (Box 158)
      - 1957-1958, (6 folders) (Box 159)
      - 1959-1960, (6 folders) (Box 160)
      - 1961-1966, (8 folders) (Box 161)
      - 1967-1968, (6 folders) (Box 162)
      - 1969-1986, (3 folders) (Box 163)
      - Undated, (5 folders); (7 folders); (8 folders); (6 folders); (10 folders) (Box 164, Box 165, Box 166, Box 167, Box 168, Box 169, Box 170)
    - Video appearances, 1981-1988 (Box 171)
  - Narration
    - Audiovisual presentations
      - Acoustiguide tours, 1963-1964, 1986, undated
      - American Museum-Hayden Planetarium sky show, 1984-1990
      - "The Beginning and End of the World," planetarium show, 1971-1972
      - "The City of the Gods," Teotihuacan, Mexico, sound and light show, 1966-1969, undated
      - Missouri Arts Council slide show, 1983
      - "Tombstone: The Town Too Tough to Die" diorama, 1964
      - United States Navy, multi-image presentation for Trident Guidance Team, 1983
      - United Technologies, Pratt & Whitney interactive videodisc training program, 1985
      - UCLA Art Council, sound and light show, 1987
      - Vanderbilt Planetarium sky show, 1988
      - Vincent Price's Monster Manor, Six Flags Stars Hall of Fame, 1982
      - Walt Disney Imagineering projects, 1990
      - Walters Art Gallery, Baltimore, Md., multimedia show, 1981
    - Corporate and institutional films
      - Anna Kaseman Hospital, Albuquerque, N. Mex., 1971
      - Associated Funeral Director's Service, 1986
      - DeYoung Museum, San Francisco, Calif., 1966
      - Interior Department, Institute of American Indian Arts, 1970
      - Miscellaneous, 1986, undated
      - Northeast Missouri State University, Kirksville, Mo., 1983-1984
      - Orange Coast College, Costa Mesa, Calif., undated
      - Sophia T. Salvin Elementary School, Los Angeles, Calif., 1972
    - Live performances (Box 172)
      - Baltimore Symphony Orchestra, Baltimore, Md., 1979-1981
      - Baton Rouge Symphony Orchestra, Baton Rouge, La., 1981
      - California Chamber Symphony, Los Angeles, Calif., 1965
      - Columbus Symphony Orchestra, Columbus, Ohio, 1978-1980
      - Denver Symphony Orchestra, Denver, Colo., 1973-1975
      - Desert Symphony, Palm Springs, Calif., 1983-1984
      - Harrisburg Symphony Orchestra, Harrisburg, Pa., 1983
      - Houston Symphony, Houston, Tex., 1986
      - Kansas City Philharmonic, Kansas City, Mo., 1981
      - Los Angeles Master Chorale with the Sinfonia Orchestra of Los Angeles, Los Angeles, Calif., 1965
      - Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra, Los Angeles, Calif., 1961-1962
      - Miscellaneous orchestras, 1959, 1975-1986
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Oklahoma Symphony Orchestra, Oklahoma City, Okla., 1975-1976
      - Poetry readings, 1973-1975
      - Rockford Symphony Orchestras, Rockford, Ill., 1977
      - St. Louis Symphony Orchestra, St. Louis, Mo., 1963-1964, 1971-1973
      - San Diego State College, San Diego, Calif., 1968
      - San Francisco Pops, San Francisco, Calif., 1979
      - San Jose Symphony Orchestra, San Jose, Calif., 1984-1986
      - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, Seattle, Wash., 1983-1984
      - Waco Symphony Association, Waco, Tex., 1983
      - Yale Symphony Orchestra, New Haven, Conn., 1984-1985
    - Miscellaneous projects and voice tracks, 1951, 1967-1990, undated
    - Videotapes (Box 173)
      - "Escapes," short story anthology, 1984-1986
      - House of Seven Gables tour, 1988-1989
      - Nishika instructional/sales, 1989
      - Simon & Schuster Communications, 1985
      - "Strange but True Football Stories," 1987
  - Plays
    - The American Way, 1940
    - Anatol, 1935
    - Angel Street, 1941
    - Anita, 1955
    - Ardele, 1974-1975
    - Billy Budd, 1955
    - Black Eyed Susan, 1954, undated
    - Charley's Aunt, 1976
    - Chicago, 1935
    - The Cocktail Party, 1951
    - Damn Yankees, 1976-1978
    - Darling of the Day, 1967-1968, (8 folders) See also Container 179, Married Alive (Box 174)
    - Death Takes a Holiday, 1954
    - Diversions and Delights See also Container 149, Kolmar-Luth Entertainment (Box 175)
      - Bookings and tour materials, 1977-1983, undated, (3 folders)
      - Contracts, 1979-1980, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1977, (4 folders)
        - 1978-1983, undated, (4 folders) (Box 176)
      - Miscellany, 1977-1981, undated
      - Programs, 1977-1983, (3 folders)
      - Publicity (Box 177)
        - Activities, 1977-1982, undated
        - Miscellaneous clippings, 1977-1983, undated, (8 folders)
        - Promotional material and advertisements, 1977-1983
          - See also Oversize
        - Reviews, 1977-1982, undated, (6 folders) (Box 178)
    - Don Juan in Hell, 1952
    - Eden End, 1937
    - Elizabeth the Queen, 1936, 1940
    - Goodbye Again, 1952
    - Heartbreak House, 1938
    - The Lady Has a Heart, 1937-1938
    - The Lady of La Paz, 1937
    - The Lady's Not for Burning, 1954
    - The Last of My Solid Gold Watches, 1947, undated
    - Mamba's Daughters, 1939
    - Married Alive, 1967-1968, (2 folders) See also Container 174, Darling of the Day (Box 179)
    - The Mistress of the Inn, 1939
    - Oliver! 1970-1976, undated, (4 folders) See also Oversize
    - Outward Bound, 1938-1939
    - Parnell, 1936-1938
    - The Passing of the Third Floor Back, 1937
    - Peter Pan, 1964-1965, (2 folders)
    - Poet's Corner, 1940
    - Princess Turandot, 1937
    - Romance, 1937
    - Shoemaker's Holiday, 1937-1938
    - Victoria Regina, 1935-1937, (3 folders) (Box 180)
    - Visit to a Small Planet, 1958
    - What Every Woman Knows, 1936
    - The Wild Duck, 1937
    - The Winslow Boy, 1954
  - Public service announcements
    - Art museums, 1966, 1979-1980, 1986-1990, undated
    - Colleges, 1975-1985
    - Elections and voting, 1980, 1988
    - Goodwill Industries, 1976, 1986
    - Miscellaneous campaigns, 1963, 1973-1987
    - National Easter Seal Society, 1985-1986
    - Treasury Department, 1971-1972, 1984-1985
    - UNICEF, 1987
  - Radio
    - American Red Cross programs, 1937, 1950
    - "The Bible Answers," 1971, (3 folders)
    - Busch-Reisinger organ series, 1986-1987 (Box 181)
    - "Conversation," 1957
    - "The Croupier," 1949
    - "Magic Key of RCA," 1937
    - Miscellaneous appearances, 1937-1990, undated
    - "Night of the Wolf," 1975-1984
    - "The Price of Fear," 1973, 1983-1991, (3 folders)
    - Salvation Army programs, 1953-1963, 1986-1989
    - "Tales of the Unexplained," undated
    - Voice of America
      - "Life on the Mississippi," 1983-1984
      - "Wine of the Country," 1968
    - "Where There's a Will," 1954
  - Sound Recordings
    - "America the Beautiful," 1961-1969
    - Columbia Records Panorama Colorslide Program, 1960-1961
    - Entertainment Marketing Company, Inc. (EMCI), spoken word cassettes, 1983-1986, undated (Box 182)
    - "His Son," 1969-1975, 1990, (2 folders)
    - Miscellaneous and unidentified, 1956-1985, undated
    - "The Monster Mash," 1976-1977, undated
    - "Thriller," 1983-1985, undated
    - "Witchcraft-Magic," 1969-1971, undated
    - "Witches, Ghosts, and Goblins," 1972-1974
    - "The World of Century Twentyfirst," 1962
  - Television
    - "ABC Weekend Special," 1984
    - Academy Award specials, 1969-1971
    - "Alfred Hitchcock Presents," 1957 (Box 183)
    - "Alice Cooper-The Nightmare," 1975
    - "An American Portrait," 1985
    - "Anyone for Tennyson?" 1976
    - "Appreciating Art," 1990-1991
    - "Art Linkletter's House Party," 1960, 1965
    - "Batman," 1966-1967, 1988-1991, (5 folders)
    - "Beware of the Devil," 1980, undated
    - "Bicentennial Minute," 1974
    - "The Bionic Woman," 1976
    - "Blacke's Magic," 1986
    - "Bob Hope Special," 1976 (Box 184)
    - "The Boo Show," 1971, undated
    - "The Brady Bunch," 1972
    - "Caravan around the World," 1966
    - "The Carol Burnett Show," 1972-1977, (4 folders)
    - "Cavalcade of Books," 1962-1964
    - "Celebrity Gourmet," 1982
    - "Chevrolet Presents the Golddiggers," 1972, (2 folders) (Box 185)
    - "Chevy Mystery Show," 1960
    - "Circus of the Stars," 1982-1983, 1990
    - "Collector's Item," 1957, (2 folders)
    - "Columbo," 1973
    - "The Compleat Gilbert and Sullivan," 1982-1987
    - "Cooking Price-Wise," 1970-1971
    - "Crossroads," 1955-1956, (2 folders) (Box 186)
    - "The Curiosity Shop," 1971
    - "Daniel Boone," 1968
    - "The Danny Kaye Show," 1964-1966, (5 folders)
    - "Dateline Hollywood," 1967
    - "Dating Game," 1972
    - "The David Frost Revue," 1970-1971
    - "The Dean Martin Comedy Hour," 1973 (Box 187)
    - "Death Trap," 1975-1977
    - "Dee Time," 1968-1969, undated
    - "Della," 1969
    - "Dinah," 1978
    - "Dinah's Place," 1970, 1973
    - "Don't Ask Me, Ask God," 1983-1984
    - "The Ed Sullivan Show," 1968
    - "Ellery Queen," 1975-1976
    - "Entertainment Tonight," 1985-1986
    - "ESP," 1958
    - "An Evening at the Improv," 1981
    - "An Evening with Edgar Allan Poe," 1969-1970
    - "Eye on Art: The St. Louis Art Scene," 1967
    - "F Troop," 1966-1967
    - "Faerie Tale Theatre," 1983-1984, undated
    - "Family Classics," 1960 (Box 188)
    - "Family Feud," 1981-1984
    - "Ford Startime," 1959-1960, (2 folders)
    - "The General Electric Theater," 1955-1958, (3 folders)
    - "Get Smart," 1969
    - "The Ghost Ship," 1986
    - "The Good Guys," 1969
    - "A Half Hour to Kill," 1958
    - "Have Gun Will Travel," 1957
    - "Heart of Justice," 1991 (Box 189)
    - "The Heiress," 1969, (3 folders)
    - "Here Comes Peter Cottontail," 1970-1971
    - "Here's Lucy," 1970
    - "Hollywood Squares," 1966-1976, 1987-1988, undated
    - "The Horror Hall of Fame," 1974
    - "The House on Art Hill," 1964, (2 folders)
    - "If These Walls Could Speak," 1965-1969, (2 folders) (Box 190)
    - "The Jack Benny Television Program," 1953-1965, (3 folders)
    - "The Jack Paar Show," 1959-1960
    - "The Jimmy Stewart Show," 1971
    - "Johnny Mann's Stand Up and Cheer," 1972
    - "The Late Show Starring Joan Rivers," 1987
    - "Life with Linkletter," 1970
    - "The Lorax," 1971
    - "Love, American Style," 1970
    - "The Love Boat," 1978
    - "Lux Video Theatre," 1954 (Box 191)
    - "The Man from U.N.C.L.E.," 1965
    - "Max," 1969
    - "The Merv Griffin Show," 1967-1979, 1986
    - "The Mike Douglas Show," 1967-1972
    - "The Milton Berle Show," 1966
    - Miscellaneous
      - Appearances, 1951-1991, undated, (3 folders)
      - Pilots and program proposals, 1964-1982, undated (Box 192)
      - Television-related materials, 1956-1990, undated, (2 folders)
    - "The Mod Squad," 1970-1971
    - "The Movie Game," 1970-1971, undated
    - "Movie of the Weekend," 1971
    - "The Muppet Show," 1976-1978, 1986
    - "Mysteries of the Supernatural," 1983
    - "Mystery!" 1980-1991, undated, (1 folder); (8 folders); (5 folders) (Box 193, Box 194)
    - "NBC Matinee Theater," 1958
    - "Night Gallery," 1971-1972, (2 folders)
    - "Night of 100 Stars," 1985
    - "Odyssey," 1957
    - "Off the Set," 1957
    - "Once upon a Midnight Dreary," 1979-1980
    - "Out of Control," 1983-1984
    - "Over Easy," 1977-1982
    - "People and Their Dream Houses," 1983
    - "Person to Person," 1958-1959 (Box 195)
    - "Personality," 1969
    - "The Pet Set," 1971
    - "The Picture Show," 1986-1988
    - "Playhouse 90," 1957
    - Public television fund-raising appearances, 1982-1988
    - "Read, Write and Draw," 1987-1990, undated, (2 folders)
    - "The Reader's Digest on Television," 1955, (2 folders)
    - "The Red Skelton Hour," 1958-1968, (3 folders); (6 folders) (Box 196)
    - "The Red Skelton Show," 1969-1971, (3 folders)
    - "The Red Skelton Special," 1966
    - "Red Skelton's Christmas Dinner," 1981
    - "Richiardi's Chamber of Horror & Illusion," 1979 (Box 197)
    - "Riverboat," 1959
    - "Rowan and Martin's Laugh In," 1968-1972, 1987, (2 folders)
    - "Schlitz Playhouse," 1957-1958
    - "Science Fiction Theatre," 1955-1956, (2 folders)
    - "Shower of Stars," 1957
    - "The 64,000 Challenge," 1956-1959
    - "The Snoop Sisters," 1973-1974, (2 folders) (Box 198)
    - "The Sonny & Cher Comedy Hour," 1973
    - "The Sorcerer's Apprentice," undated
    - "Soundsations," 1976-1977
    - "Spiro Agnew Is a Riot," 1970
    - "Starquest," undated
    - "The Steve Allen Show," 1964, undated
    - "Symbols of Lives Past-the Rambova Collection," 1979
    - "Talent Scouts," 1966
    - "Tales from the Vatican Collection," 1980-1983
    - "Talisman," 1951
    - "The Taste of Angels," 1978-1979, (2 folders)
    - "Thicke of the Night," 1984
    - "The 13 Ghosts of Scooby Doo," 1985
    - "Time Express," 1979, (6 folders) (Box 199)
    - "Tommy Cooper Show," 1969
    - "Tonight Show," 1962-1988, undated, (2 folders)
    - "Trapper John, M.D.," 1982
    - "Vincent Price Is in the Country," 1971, undated
    - "Vincent Price's Dracula," 1981-1983
    - "Vincent Price's Halloween Thriller," 1984-1987
    - "Voyage to the Bottom of the Sea," 1967 (Box 200)
    - "The Wild, Weird World of Dr. Goldfoot," 1965, (2 folders)
    - "World of Poetry," 1976-1977
    - "The World of Vincent Price," 1977
    - "You Don't Say," 1967-1968
- Subject File, 1920-1992 (Box 200-230)
  Correspondence, memoranda, reports, financial records, receipts, brochures, appointment books and calendars, certificates, notes, clippings, printed matter, and miscellaneous materials.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization, person, activity, topic, or type of material.
  - Academy Awards (Box 200)
    - Ballots, 1968-1971
    - Ceremonies, 1968, 1977-1982, 1989
  - All Nations Fair, Los Angeles County, Calif., 1962-1964
  - The American Federation of Arts, 1948-1959
  - American Institute of Interior Designers, 1962-1972
  - American Institute of Wine and Food, 1985-1989
  - American International Pictures, 1962-1984, 1991, undated, (2 folders) (Box 201)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1972-1976
  - Animals in art, 1967-1968
  - Appointment books and calendars, 1948-1949, 1958-1960, 1964, 1971, 1973, (6 folders)
  - Archives of American Art (Box 202)
    - 1954-1965, (6 folders)
    - 1966-1984, undated, (4 folders) (Box 203)
  - Art collection
    - Correspondence, 1941-1990, undated, (3 folders)
    - Gifts, 1945-1988, undated For additional material see Container 210, Vincent Price Gallery
    - Lists, circa 1927-1967, (3 folders) For additional material see Container 214, Appraisals (Box 204)
    - Loans
      - 1940, 1948-1965, (5 folders)
      - 1966-1991, (4 folders) (Box 205)
    - Miscellaneous records
      - 1936-1966, (7 folders)
      - 1967-1974, 1986, undated, (5 folders) (Box 206)
    - Modigliani, Amedeo, file, 1965, undated
    - Piranesi, Giambattista, exhibit, 1969-1970, undated
    - Traveling exhibit
      - Administrative material, 1967-1970, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1971, (3 folders) (Box 207)
      - Descriptive material, undated
      - Framing, 1967, undated
  - Artists, 1962-1989, undated, (2 folders)
  - Barrow, W. J., manuscript restoration, 1963-1964
  - Beverly Hills Jewelry Centre, Beverly Hills, Calif., 1965, undated
  - Biographical material, 1956-1990, undated
  - Business and gift cards, 1955-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 208)
  - California Wine Institute
    - General, 1965-1970, undated, (2 folders)
    - Wine tasting party, May 13, 1967
  - Center of American Living, 1966-1970, undated
  - Charitable sponsorships and donations, 1950-1972, 1984-1991, undated
  - Childhood miscellany, 1923, undated
  - Christmas card list, 1964-1967 (Box 209)
  - Community School, St. Louis, Mo., 1920, 1984-1985, 1990
  - Cooper, Charlotte, 1923, 1935, 1962-1966, undated
  - Courtauld Institute of Art, University of London, London, England, 1934, 1986-1987, undated
  - Denver Art Museum, Denver, Colo., 1971-1985, 1991, undated
  - Drawings and sketches
    - By others, 1963-1991, undated See also Oversize
    - By Price, 1928, undated
  - Dreyfuss, Henry and Doris, 1962-1974, undated, (2 folders)
  - East Los Angeles College, Monterey Park, Calif. (Box 210)
    - Miscellaneous activities, 1948-1963, 1983-1987
    - Vincent Price Gallery, 1958-1991, undated, (4 folders) See also Oversize
  - The English Players, 1965-1967
  - Ethnic Art Council of Los Angeles, 1966-1974
  - Fan materials
    - Clubs
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, 1983, 1989-1991
      - The Vincent Price Appreciation Society, 1988-1991
      - Vincent Price Official International Fan Club, 1947
    - Correspondence, select and unusual, 1963-1970, undated
    - Miscellany, 1962-1975, undated, (2 folders) See also Oversize (Box 211)
  - Financial records
    - Personal
      - 1936, 1949-1969, (3 folders)
      - 1970-1982, 1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 212)
    - Vincent Price Enterprises, 1964-1973
  - Fine Arts Committee for the White House, 1962
  - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco, Calif., 1985-1990, undated
  - Garden of the Patriots, Cape Coral, Fla., 1965-1967
  - Governor's Conference on California Beauty, citizen's advisory committee, 1965-1966, undated, (2 folders)
  - Hazan, Marcella, cooking courses, Venice, Italy, 1983-1990 (Box 213)
  - Heard Museum, Phoenix, Ariz., 1966
  - Hollywood Chamber of Commerce, Hollywood, Calif.
    - Miscellaneous activities, 1963-1975
    - Walk of Fame, 1960, 1971-1973, 1986-1990